mylelojobs.com 2016-11-24

# Mylelo Jobs - Privacy Policy

## Our Policy

### WHAT THIS PRIVACY POLICY COVERS

Mylelo takes your privacy seriously. Please read the following to learn more about our privacy policy.

**How Mylelo Uses Your Personal Information**

This policy covers how Mylelo treats personal information that Mylelo collects and receives, including information related to your past use of Mylelo products and services. Personal information is information about you that is personally identifiable like your name, address, email address, or phone number, and that is not otherwise publicly available.

**This privacy policy only applies to Mylelo**

This policy does not apply to the practices of companies that Mylelo does not own or control, or to people that Mylelo does not employ or manage.

### INFORMATION COLLECTION AND USE

**General**

Mylelo collects personal information when you register with Mylelo, when you use Mylelo products or services, when you visit Mylelo pages or the pages of certain Mylelo partners, and when you enter promotions or sweepstakes. Mylelo may combine information about you that we have with information we obtain from business partners or other companies. 

When you register we ask for information such as your name, email address, birth date, gender, industry, and personal interests. For some financial products and services we might also ask for your address, Social Security number, and information about your assets. When you register with Mylelo and sign in to our services, you are not anonymous to us. 

Mylelo collects information about your transactions with us and with some of our business partners, including information about your use of financial products and services that we offer.

Mylelo automatically receives and records information from your computer and browser, including your IP address, Mylelo cookie information, software and hardware attributes, and the page you request.

Mylelo uses information for the following general purposes: to customize the advertising and content you see, fulfill your requests for products and services, improve our services, contact you, conduct research, and provide anonymous reporting for internal and external clients. 

### INFORMATION SHARING AND DISCLOSURE

Mylelo does not rent, sell, or share personal information about you with other people or non-affiliated companies except to provide products or services you've requested, when we have your permission, or under the following circumstances:

  * We provide the information to trusted partners who work on behalf of or with Mylelo under confidentiality agreements. These companies may use your personal information to help Mylelo communicate with you about offers from Mylelo and our marketing partners. However, these companies do not have any independent right to share this information. 
  * We respond to subpoenas, court orders, or legal process, or to establish or exercise our legal rights or defend against legal claims. 
  * We believe it is necessary to share information in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, violations of Mylelo's terms of use, or as otherwise required by law. 
  * We transfer information about you if Mylelo is acquired by or merged with another company. In this event, Mylelo will notify you before information about you is transferred and becomes subject to a different privacy policy. 

Mylelo displays targeted advertisements based on personal information. Advertisers (including ad serving companies) may assume that people who interact with, view, or click targeted ads meet the targeting criteria—for example, women ages 18-24 from a particular geographic area. 

  * Mylelo does not provide any personal information to the advertiser when you interact with or view a targeted ad. However, by interacting with or viewing an ad you are consenting to the possibility that the advertiser will make the assumption that you meet the targeting criteria used to display the ad. 
  * Mylelo advertisers include financial service providers (such as banks, insurance agents, stock brokers and mortgage lenders) and non-financial companies (such as stores, airlines, and software companies). 

Mylelo works with vendors, partners, advertisers, and other service providers in different industries and categories of business.

Return to Top

### COOKIES

Mylelo may set and access Mylelo cookies on your computer.

Mylelo lets other companies that show advertisements on some of our pages set and access their cookies on your computer. Other companies' use of their cookies is subject to their own privacy policies, not this one. Advertisers or other companies do not have access to Mylelo's cookies.

**Your Ability to Edit Your Account Information and Preferences**   
**General**

You can edit your Mylelo Account Information, including your marketing preferences, at any time. 

New categories of marketing communications might be added to the Marketing Preferences page from time to time. Users who visit this page can opt out of receiving future marketing communications from these new categories or they can unsubscribe by following instructions contained in the messages they receive. 

We reserve the right to send you certain communications relating to the Mylelo service, such as service announcements, administrative messages and the Mylelo Newsletter, that are considered part of your Mylelo account, without offering you the opportunity to opt out of receiving them. 

Return to Top

### CONFIDENTIALITY AND SECURITY

We limit access to personal information about you to employees who we believe reasonably need to come into contact with that information to provide products or services to you or in order to do their jobs. 

We have physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards that comply with federal regulations to protect personal information about you. 

Return to Top

### CHANGES TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY

Mylelo may update this policy. We will notify you about significant changes in the way we treat personal information by sending a notice to the primary email address specified in your Mylelo account or by placing a prominent notice on our site.
